《黑镜》
《虚伪的分数》
- 嗨 莱希 - 嗨
- Hey, Lacie! - Hey!
（给简打了五分）
（给克洛伊打了五分）
（给约翰尼打了五分）
（莱希 4.243分）
赖安
Ryan?
Ryan!
- 我拿着炸弹呢 - 你搞毛啊
- I was holding a bomb! - Come on!
抱歉 伙计们
Sorry, guys.
房东今天会让买家过来 所以 你给我裤子
Landlord is sending buyers over today so… put your pants on.
要是我不穿裤子的话 也许能吓跑他们 我们就能留下了
Maybe if I don't, it'll scare 'em off and we can stay here.
这可不行 赖安 租约还有四周就到期了
Not an option, Ryan. Lease is up in four weeks.
嘿 我这是在为你考虑 我有地方去的好吗
Hey, I'm thinking of you. I've got somewhere to go.
纳特的室友在凤凰城找了份工作 所以他的房间归我了
Nate's roommate took a job in Phoenix so I get his place.
- 好吧 - 你慢了吧
- Okay. - Now who's the slow poke?
我 午餐时间我会去看房的 迟点再聊
I'm… seeing some places over lunch. Catch you later.
抱歉 那是我姐姐
Sorry, that was my sister.
对 对 我知道你想上她
Yeah. Yeah, I bet you'd love to.
茉莉花茶
Jasmine tea?
（给山姆打了五分）
（给基斯打了五分）
一份磨砂奶咖
And that's one Brushed Suede.
你想要一块饼干吗
You want a cookie with that?
（杰克 3.797分）
- 免费哦 - 太棒了
- It's on the house. - Sounds awesome.
（给杰克打了五分）
- JJ 明天见 - 明天见 莱希
- See you tomorrow, JJ. - See you, Lacie.
我看见你孩子戴着消防帽的视频了 真是可爱到爆
Oh, I saw your boy in the fire hat just now! So cute!
对啊 他可厉害了
Yeah, he's really something.
（莱希·庞德 磨砂奶咖配曲奇饼超级棒）
（成功上传）
（你已被评分）
嘿 莱希
Hey, Lacie!
- 贝茨 见到你真高兴 - 我也是
- Bets, it's great to see you! - You too.
（贝芬妮·琼斯）
煎饼怎么样啦
How's Pancakes?
它超级搞笑 特别好玩 全世界最棒的喵
He's hilarious. Such a funny cat. Just the best.
- 你还在霍迪卡吗 - 是啊
- Are you still at Hoddicker? - Mm-hmm.
- 是啊 那里挺好的 - 那可真好
- Yeah. It's going pretty great. - Good to hear.
- 所以你怎么回来了 - 新工作 第一天
- So what brings you back here? - New job, first day.
- 第一天吗 - 在布兰克曼-哈珀尔
- First day? - At Blankman-Harper.
哇 顶层诶 那可真
Whoa! Top floor! That's…
- 祝你好运 - 我懂的 哈哈
- Well, good luck. - I know, right?
看到你在霍迪卡这么开心 真好
It's great you're still happy at Hoddicker.
- 暂时的啦 - 对 暂时的
- Well, maybe not forever. - No, not forever.
- 只是现在还在 - 对 现在而已 没问题的
- But for now… - It's OK for now.
现在在那里挺好的 是的 挺好的
It's great for now, yes. Yes, it is.
（莱希·庞德）
莱希 我给你买了一杯冰沙
Lacie, I got you a smoothie.
其实给大家都买了 但是还有一大堆剩下的
Got one for everyone, actually. Still a bunch of them for grabs.
（切斯特）
是农贸市场的有机货摊那边卖的
They're from the organic stall at the farmers' market.
好啊 好的
Sure. Okay.
（切斯特）
谢谢 谢谢
Thank you. Thank you.
我们现在不怎么和切斯说话
We're kind of not talking to Ches.
- 3.1分 发生了什么 - 他和戈登分手了
- 3.1? What happened? - Him and Gordon split up.
噢
Oh…
- 可怜的切斯 - 不 不 不 我们是站在戈登那边的
- Poor Ches. - No, no, no, we're all on Gordon's side.
当然啦 显而易见
Sure! Obviously.
切斯在拍马屁 想要腆着脸回来
Ches is kissing ass. Trying to scrape himself back.
当然 要是掉到二点五分以下 那就拜拜啦
Of course, if it drops below two-five, then it's… bye-bye.
（你已被评分）
你好
Hello?
- 哟 他们要买 - 谁
- Yo, they're taking it. - Who?
房东找来的那对夫妻 我听到他们说要买下这房子了
The couple the landlord sent over. I heard them talking.
好的
Okay.
好了 现在我们进入了日光厅
So, now we move into the light space area.
在这里跟心爱之人共度甜蜜时光最适合不过了
Ideal for special times with loved ones.
美食满桌 佳人相伴
Great food, great company.
用你上传的照片合成的
Sampled your photo stream to make her.
好棒的发型
Great hair!
小区成员专用的沙龙提供的免费造型
Styled free of charge at the members' salon.
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
真有趣
It's hilarious!
你喜欢他吗
You like him?
- 他还好啦 - 公寓不配送男朋友哦
- He's okay. - He doesn't come with the apartment.
但是附近有酒吧和餐厅 只限租客使用
But there is a bar and restaurant on site, tenants only.
我们营造的无与伦比的浪漫氛围能让爱情轻易萌芽
We have unparalleled metrics on romantic geneses.
我得告诉你 这的房子可是特别抢手的
I gotta say, these places are going like "that."
- 要是你感兴趣的话就千万别迟疑 - 噢 我可不止是感兴趣
- So don't delay if you're interested. - Oh, I'm more than interested.
至少六个月的标准租约
Standard occupancy on a minimum six-month contract,
价格大概是 这样
we're talking… this much.
- 多久交一次啊 - 这是每周的租金
- How often are the payments? - That's weekly.
好吧
Okay.
- 比想象中的多一点对吧 - 是啊
- A little more than expected? - Yeah.
其实是有商量余地的
There's options.
你知道我们的精英领袖项目吗
You know our Prime Influencers Programme?
- 我算是精英吗 - 不 不 不 你不算
- Do I qualify for that? - No. No, you don't.
4.5分左右才算
We'd need you around a 4.5.
4.5分吗
4.5?
到了4.5分就能打八折
Hit 4.5 and there's a 20% discount.
- 4.5分 - 对的
- 4.5. - That's right.
（鹧鸪湾）
（奈奥米·杰恩·布雷斯托）
（保罗·马锡森）
（和内奥米·杰恩·布雷斯托一起共享美丽黄昏）
鹈鹕湾 那是什么 什么优生项目吗
Pelican Cove? What is this? A eugenics programme?
- 一个生活社区 - 没有人会这么开心
- A lifestyle community. - No one is this happy.
（赖安）
一个拿着气球的两岁小孩都不可能开心
A two-year-old with a fucking balloon isn't this happy.
那里其实蛮有意思的
It's actually a pretty cool place.
你够格住进去么
Like you'd even qualify.
我无能为力 先生
There's nothing I can do, sir.
还是有希望的 你明显是个勇于尝试的人
Well, it's not hopeless, you're clearly a tryer.
你光看看我就有这样的感觉吗
That's the sense you get just from… me?
我看的是你的口碑报告分析
From your rep report analytics.
要是我们深度分析你的数据 你的人气弧相当扎实
If we drill down into the numbers, you've got a solid popularity arc here.
整体趋势很强 让我们看看最近二十四小时
Strong overall trajectory. Let's just look at the last 24 hours.
你看 甚至
You see, even…
那是什么 早上8点40分 你在社交平台上很努力啊
What's that? 8:40 a.m. You're working hard on your socials.
- 很好的一步尝试 - 好的
- Great little uptake there. - Okay.
有几个小差评啊 你在开车的时候超人车了吗
Couple of minor dings there. You cut someone off in traffic?
噢 只是工作上的事情
Oh, just a workplace thing.
好吧 让我们看看你的影响范围
Okay. Let's check on your sphere of influence.
看看大范围
Let me zoom out here.
周边关系很好啊 陌生人喜欢你 加分哦
Great peripherals. Strangers like you, that's a plus.
- 好友圈子也很健康 很好 - 谢谢
- Healthy inner circle. It's good. - Thank you.
还有很长的路要走 但是4.5分绝对是有可能达到的
There's a ways to go, but 4.5 is certainly achievable.
你觉得得花多久呢
How long do you think?
- 达到4.5分吗 - 嗯
- To hit 4.5? - Mm-hmm.
嗯 如果能避免重大挫折
Well, barring a major setback,
被当众羞辱之类的事 大概一年半左右吧
a public disgrace kind of deal, I'd say 18 months or so.
噢 我需要短期就能提升 要很短
Oh, I need more short term. Like… much more.
那你需要一点助推了
Then you'll need a boost.
- 什么样的助推 - 这个嘛
- What kind of a boost? - Well…
你大部分的社交都局限在你的好友圈
Most of your interactions are confined to your inner circle.
而他们大部分都是 原谅我的用词 中下层的人
and they're largely, pardon the term, mid-to low-range folks.
你的社交外围圈也一样
Same with your outer circle.
你有一堆来自服务行业的工人的互相五星好评
You've got a ton of reciprocal five stars from service industry workers,
但是除此之外就没别的了
but there's not much else.
至少目前是这样
At least as far as I can see.
所以你需要在质量方面做出提升
So in terms of quality, you could use a punch up right there.
最好是就是从优质的人那里得到好评
Ideally, that's up votes from quality people.
- 优质的人 - 评分在四星高分段的精英
- Quality people? - High fours.
打动那些高端人群 你的人气弧就能一下上去
Impress those up-scale folks, you'll gain velocity on your arc.
这就是你需要的助推
and there's your boost.
（已给奈奥米5星）
- 嗨 JJ - 嗨 莱希
- Oh, hi, JJ! - Hey, Lacie!
- 基思 你好 - 莱希
- Keith! Hello. - Lacie!
- 你今天好漂亮 - 谢谢
- You look great today. - Thank you!
- 门不开 我现在才2.4分 - 对不起 切斯 我迟到了
- Door won't open. I'm on 2.4. - Sorry, Ches. I'm late.
我只需要几颗星星 求求你了
I just need some stars, please!
卧槽
Fuck!
- 噢 嗨 - 嗨
- Oh, hi! - Hi!
- 布兰克曼那怎么样 - 非常好
- How's it going at Blankman? - Just great.
- 嗯 我就知道你在那会干得 挺好的 - 谢谢
- Well, I bet you work… good there. - Thank you.
要来一个羊角面包吗
Would you like a croissant?
咖啡店多给了我一个
They gave me an extra at the coffee place.
- 噢不用了 我吃过了 - 噢 好吧 没事 嗯
- Oh, no, I already ate. - Okay, sure. All good. Yes.
嗯
Yeah.
好吧 我到了 那么
Well, here's me, so…
（达尼·琼斯）
不要用力过猛了 卑躬屈膝不可能赢得尊重
Don't try too hard. It's impossible to respect.
四星精英们老远就能看出来了 做自己就好
High fours can smell it a mile off. Just be you.
真诚的表现 这才是关键
Authentic gestures, that's the key.
- 时间到了 晚点再联系你 - 噢 我能不能问一下
- That's time up, I'll catch you later. - Oh, could I just ask…
（莱斯·庞德）
（奈奥米·杰恩·布雷斯托）
（保罗做了超棒的橄榄酱）
（保罗·马西森）
（莱斯·庞德）
“破布先生”
… "Mr. Rags."
（图片已上传）
（0个人给你的图片打五星）
（1个人给你的图片打五星）
糟糕
Shit!
- 这特么是什么玩意 - 橄榄酱 来点吗
- What the fuck is that? - Tapenade. Want some?
你是谁啊
Who even are you?
我只是想吃了 赖安
It's just something I wanna eat, Ryan.
（内奥米·布雷斯托 来电）
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
- 这是什么 - 奈奥米
- What is it? - Naomi!
我去
Shit!
经典 完美的奈奥米 你们还在联系吗
Old school, el perfecto Naomi? You guys keep in contact?
赖安 你走开 走
Ryan, just go! Go!
- 我的天 - 奈奈 你好吗
- Oh, my God! - Nay-Nay, how are you?
我只是随便做点小零食
I was just fixing myself a snack.
噢 莱希 我能说我看到你好高兴吗
Oh, Lace, could I just say I am so happy to see your face?
- 我也是啊 我们已经有 - 有很久不见了
- Me too. It's been… - Too long.
- 太久了 - 都怪我
- Way too long. - And that's my fault.
- 不 怪我 就是平时太 - 平时太
- No, it's mine. Everything is just so… - Everything's just so…
每天忙到爆 看见你真好
Crazy! Oh, it's so good to see you.
当你上传了那张破布先生的照片
When you posted that Mr. Rags photo…
对 破布先生
I know, Mr. Rags!
我必须给你打电话
I just had to call.
跟你聊聊 因为
and talk to you because…
哇啊
Whoo-hoo!
哇 好大的戒指
Wow! That's a… big ring!
恭喜 你嫁给的是 保罗吗
Congratulations! Who's the, um… Paul?
他很棒 非常聪明 又贴心
He is great. So smart. Just sweet.
我知道你会很喜欢他的
I know you're gonna love him.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
那么 不论如何 重头日是
So, anyways, the big day…
对 是什么时候
Yes, when is it?
我们下个月就要结婚了
So, we're getting married in a month.
就在这个岛上
on his family's estate.
他家的庄园办婚礼
up here on the island.
在忍冬的玛丽港外 你听说过吗
This place outside Port Mary, Honeysuckle. You heard of it?
没有 但
No, but…
好吧 这是个私人小岛
Well, it's a private island.
快看
Take a looooook!
哇 这真是
Oh, wow! That is…
我懂 嗯 所以 你能来吗
I know, right? So… can you make it?
你开玩笑吗 当然能
Are you kidding? Of course.
太棒了 真好 我在想 如果
Great, cool, cos I was wondering if…
莱希 你觉得
Lace, do you think…
你愿意做我的首席伴娘吗
Would you be my maid of honour?
你认真的吗
Seriously?
我的天哪
Oh, my God.
我是说 你现在都有那么棒的朋友了 你确定吗
I mean, you've got such cool friends now. Are you sure?
还记得我们11岁的时候 策划着我们梦想的婚礼吗
Remember when we used to plan our dream weddings when we were, like, 11?
- 我知道 但我们这么久没 - 我不知道 看见破布先生
- I know but we haven't s… - I don't know, just seeing Mr. Rags…
所有的记忆都回来了
All the memories. It just brought things home.
哦 奈奈
Oh, Nay-Nay.
我知道我们很久很久没有联系了
I know we haven't kept in touch as much as I'd have liked.
全怪我 但那天非常重要
and that is totally my fault, but this is a big day.
一生中屈指可数的大日子 我希望我的老朋友在我身边 交情最久的老朋友
A big life day and I want my oldest friend with me, my oldest friend.
我希望你能在我身边
I want you by my side.
天哪 谢谢你
Oh, my God. Thank you.
我需要做什么
What do I have to…
没什么 主要是致辞
Not much to it. A speech, mainly.
致辞 当然可以
Speech? Of course!
嗯哼 会有多少人出席
Mm-hmm. How big's the crowd?
- 噢天哪 大概有 - 几百人吧
- Oh, my gosh, like… - hundreds!
这是份疯狂的宾客名单 我现在发给你
It's a crazy guest list. I'll send it now.
保罗邀请了好多人 我不想说他们有什么了不起的
Paul's invited so many, I don't want to call them big deals,
但他们都是4.7分 或者更高
but they're all, like, 4.7 or above.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
奈奈 我不会让你失望的
Nay-Nay, I will not let you down.
别太紧张 就说说从前的回忆
Don't sweat too much! Just talk about old memories.
- 好的 - 说说我们的过去 那些故事
- Sure. - How we were, any old things.
- 懂了 - 我会发给你一些过往的趣事
- Gotcha. - I'll ping you some anecdotes.
- 太好了 - 你穿几号的衣服
- That would be great. - And what's your dress size?
呃
Oh, um…
那我就直接给你件4号的
I'll tell you what, I'll just send you a four.
- 完美 - 我们有相配的伴娘礼服
- Perfect. - We got matching bridesmaids dresses.
嗯 好吧
Well, anyway…
爱你哦 小莱
Love you, Lay.
我也爱你 奈奈
You too, Nay-Nay!
哦
Oh!
再见
Bye.
那是什么 F开头的词吗
What was that? The F-word?
你们两个小娘们儿又好上了
You two pussy pals now?
闭嘴
Shut up.
- 她对你一直很刻薄 - 不 她没有
- She was always mean to you. - No, she wasn't.
- 她写的那首诗 - 那只是个玩笑
- She had that rhyme about you. - That was a game.
- 那她剪你头发呢 - 我让她剪的
- What about when she cut your hair? - I asked her to.
她睡了格雷格
She fucked Greg.
她 她没睡格雷格
She… did not fuck Greg.
她真火辣 这个我承认
She looked hot. I'll give her that.
（婚礼宾客名册）
好吧
Okay.
厉害啊
Impressive.
- 嗯哼 天哪 嗯 可以可以 - 嗯哼
- Uh-huh. Jesus. Yeah, that'd do it. - Mm-hmm.
这里是鹈鹕湾
Pelican Cove.
卡罗尔 我是莱希 昨天去看的房 我要租下
Carole, it's Lacie. Saw the place yesterday. I wanna take it.
太棒了
That's fantastic!
呃 你现在还是4.2分 这
Uh… Oh, I see you're still on a 4.2. Is that, um…
对 我决定了 现在就把押金打过去
Yep, I'm on it, just gonna transfer the deposit now.
- 嗯 好的 - 耶
- Well, okay. - Yes!
在这个世界上 我们都过于关注自己
In this world, we're all so caught up in our own heads.
却容易忽视那些真实的 重要的东西
It's easy to lose sight of what's real. What matters.
但今天当我站在这里
But as I stand here today…
看到了保罗给奈奥米的生活带来的欢乐
seeing the joy Paul has brought to Naomi's life,
我知道她对我来说真的很重要
I know she's someone who truly matters to me.
奈奈
Nay-Nay,
当时我们在艺术夏令营里 只是才五岁的小女孩
the little girl who, when we were just five-years-old in art camp,
她主动和我聊天 只因为她看见我很害怕
started talking to me because she saw I was scared.
她帮我制作了破布先生 我到现在依然保存着
The girl who helped me make Mr. Rags. I still have him.
他坐在我的桌子上
He sits on my desk and…
每天他都令我想起奈奈
every day, he reminds me of Nay-Nay.
无论是当初还是现在 她对我都很重要
What she meant to me then and now.
我非常荣幸来到这里
I am so honored to be here.
祝你从此一生幸福
and I wish you all the happiness this stupid world can muster.
我爱你 奈奈
I love you, Nay-Nay.
流眼泪是不是有点夸张啊
Is the tear too much?
你这个神经病
You fucking sociopath.
- 赖安 我的车到了 太过了吗 - 什么 眼泪 照片 破布先生吗
- Ryan, my car's here. Was it too much? - What, the tear, the photo, Mr. Rags?
我的确一直把他放在桌子上
I do keep him on my desk.
甜言蜜语是一回事 把人甜出糖尿病就太过了
There's sugary and then there's fucking diabetes.
我只不过想让她在结婚的日子里开心些
I just wanna make her happy on her wedding day.
让无法走开的四分精英用五星好评把你淹没
The captive audience of 4-point holies five-starring your ass off,
这只是附加奖励 对吧
that's just a bonus.
- 奈奥米和我曾经是最好的朋友 - 天呐
- Naomi and I were best friends. - Come on…
我希望她一切都好 我想尽我所能的表达我的情感
I wish her well and wanna express it the best I can.
好吧 如果我成功致辞了 得到几百个精英人士给我的
And, yeah, if I nail a speech and get five-starred.
五星好评 那又如何呢 这可是双赢
by hundreds of primes, so what? It's a win-win.
你指望什么呢 4.3 4.4之类的呢
What are you hoping for? Like, 4.3, 4.4?
啊 你也从你的游戏好友那里得分啊
Unh-unh. You get points from your gaming buddies.
这是一码事 我的目标更高 别老打击我
It's the same thing. Don't shit on me for aiming higher.
鹈鹕湾公寓就算是高目标了么
Pelican Cove higher?
鹈鹕湾公寓怎么了 那是很好的公寓
What's wrong with Pelican Cove? They're great apartments!
他们不过是充满假笑的牢房
They are fake-smile jail cells.
好吧 车被取消了
Great. Car cancelled.
他还给了我低分 我得重新叫车 还被给了差评
And he marked me down so now I have to book another, and I took a ding.
- 干得好 - 抱歉 但你以前正常的时候多好啊
- Great job. - I am sorry, but I miss the normal you.
在你沉迷于此之前 我们还会好好聊天 还记得吗
Before this obsession, when we had conversations, remember?
我得拿上充电器
I need my charger.
整个评分系统 只是在把你和那些
This whole ranking thing, just comparing yourself to people who…
- 你看见我的充电器了吗 - 那些假装很开心的人比来比去
- Have you seen my charger? - …only pretend to be happy.
我说了不要借这个
I said don't borrow this!
像奈奥米那样四星精英 我打赌她们的内心八成痛苦得想自杀
High fours like Naomi, I bet they're suicidal on the inside.
我的车到了 第二次
My car is here. Again.
你的鹈鹕湾押金 能退吗
Your Pelican Cove deposit, is it refundable?
如果这行不通怎么办
Like, what if this doesn't work?
- 你能别管我的破事吗 - 你是我的妹妹
- Can't you just stay out of my shit? - You're my sister!
没错 如果你真的在意我 或许你应该注意到
Yes! And if you cared about that, maybe you would've noticed.
和你住在一起对我来说并非乐事
living with you hasn't been one big rainbow sandwich for me.
你知道为什么我从来不带男生回家吗
Do you know why I never brought any guys back here?
因为我不想让他们知道我在和一个三分先生
Because I didn't want them to know I was sharing a skanky-ass cave.
分享一个脏乱不堪的房间
with Mr. Three Point Fuck.
祝你表演顺利
Good luck with your performance!
噢 嗨 嗨 我来了 我来了
Oh, hi, hi! I'm coming. I'm coming.
- 搞毛啊 - 噢 我很抱歉
- Jesus Christ! - Oh, I'm so sorry.
很好 非常好
That's great. Just great.
噢 嗨
Oh… Hi.
奈奈
Nay-Nay!
嗨 莱希 就看看你怎么样了
Hey, Lace! Just checking in.
我现在在去机场的路上
I'm on my way to the airport right now.
嗯 太好了 你准备好晚宴彩排了吗
Okay, cool, and you're all good for the rehearsal dinner?
当然啦 坐飞机大概一个小时就到了 餐厅看起来棒极了
Oh, yeah. The flight's, what, an hour? That restaurant looks so cool.
- 嗯哼 你准备好裙子了吗 - 嗯 为了以防万一
- Uh-huh. And you got the dress okay? - Mm-hmm. In my case.
- 我喜欢粉色 - 嗯哼
- I love the pink. - Uh-huh.
最后修改的演讲稿很棒
So the latest draft of the speech is great.
手写讲稿实在太酷了
Going handwritten's so cool.
那些扫描件 我的天 我都快哭了
Those scans of the page, my God, I welled up just at that.
- 噢 谢谢 - 嗯 有一件事
- Oh, thank you! - Um… just one thought.
就是在讲稿中写我帮助你克服进食障碍的地方
That whole bit where I help you with the eating disorder thing…
- 你觉得那有点 - 有点过度分享了 没错
- You think that's a little… - A little over-sharing, yeah.
你说得一点都没错 我删了
You're so right. It's gone.
好的 棒 几小时后见
Okay. Cool. Well, I'll see you in a few hours!
∮ 明天我要结婚了 ∮
∮ I'm getting married tomorrow. ∮
- 这是你的小费 - 谢谢
- And here's your tip. - Thank you.
噢 不是吧
Oh, come on.
请大家注意一下
May I have your attention, please…
- 嗨 最近怎么样 - 非常棒
- Hi there, how are you doing? - I am wonderful.
抱歉 那班航班被取消了
I am so sorry, that flight is cancelled.
- 不 不 不 不 - 顾客事务中心在另一头
- No. No, no, no. - Customer incident at the other end.
但 下班飞机是什么时候
But… So when is the next flight?
不好意思 今天航班全部客满了
Yeah, they're all kind of full.
我好几周前订的机票 我要去参加我挚友的婚礼
Uh… I booked this weeks ago. It's my best friend's wedding.
- 抱歉 - 我必须得去 必须的
- I'm sorry. - I have to get there. I have to.
好吧 让我看看有什么法子
Okay… let's see what we can do.
谢谢 太感谢了
Thank you. Thank you so much.
我看到在另一架今晚起飞的飞机上有一个备用座位
I see there's one standby seat on another plane leaving tonight.
嗯
Uh…
那是为我们的精英飞行项目的会员预留的座位
That's reserved for members of our Prime Flight Programme.
你得达到4.2以上的评分才有资格坐
You gotta be a 4.2 or over to qualify.
- 噢 我 我是4.2分 - 啊哦
- Oh, I'm… I'm a 4.2. - Uh-huh.
抱歉 你是4.183分
I'm afraid you're actually a 4.183.
噢 那不是我的错 嗯
Oh. Well, that's not my fault. Um…
有个女人给了我差评 你就不能
Some woman dinged me down in the… Can't you just…
抱歉 如果评分不到标准 系统不会允许我订票的
I'm sorry, it won't let me book it without the correct ranking.
- 但我的评分那么接近 - 我什么也做不了
- But it's so close. - There's just nothing I can do.
- 天呐 我是说 当然 - 我得请求你
- Christ, I mean, surely. - I'm gonna have to ask you.
调整一下你的措辞
to moderate your language there.
抱歉 我只是
Sorry. It's just…
我是首席伴娘 我不能错过婚礼
I'm maid of honour. I cannot miss this wedding.
我很抱歉
And I am so sorry about that.
- 你能叫你的主管来吗 - 不能
- Can you call the supervisor? - I cannot do that.
- 能叫你的主管来吗 - 我做不到
- Can you just call the supervisor? - I cannot do that.
- 特么的快给主管打电话 - 好吧 那是脏话
- Call the fucking supervisor! - Okay, that's profanity.
- 我们不能容忍爆粗口 - 抱歉 只是
- We're zero tolerance on profanity. - I'm sorry. It's just…
- 我得接待下一位乘客了 - 不 不 不 不
- I have to serve the next customer. - No, no, no, no.
- 你能走到旁边吗 女士 - 天呐 特么的快来帮帮我
- Can you step away, ma'am? - God, just fucking help me!
噢
Ooh.
我很抱歉
I'm so sorry.
- 我已经打电话叫保安了 - 噢 不 不 不 拜托千万别这么做
- I've called security. - Oh, no, no, no. Please don't do that.
我给你五星好评 五星
I'm, uh… five-starring you. Five stars.
- 这里出什么事了 汉娜 - 她恐吓我 说脏话侮辱我
- What's the issue here, Hannah? - Intimidation and profanity.
- 噢 没有 没有 我并没有恐吓你 - 闭嘴 女士
- Oh, no, no. I was not intimidating. - Don't speak, ma'am.
- 我只不过 - 女士
- I was just trying to… - Ma'am.
好吧 所以 为了恢复现场秩序
Okay. So, in order to restore calm,
作为惩罚 我将动用我机场保安的权力
I'm invoking my authority as airport security.
给你扣掉整整一分
to dock you one full ranking point as a punitive measure.
- 这是暂时措施 - 不
- This is a temporary measure. - No!
你的评分会在24小时内恢复正常
Your score reverts to normal in 24 hours.
不 不 不 但我现在就需要评分
No, no, no. But I need it now.
在这期间 所有差评会乘两倍
During this period, all down votes are subject to a times two multiplier.
两倍
Times two?
我们推荐你在这段时间避免消极评价
We recommend you avoid negative feedback at this time.
我会被双倍扣分
I'm on double damage?
请您马上离开机场
Please, remove yourself from the airport immediately.
好了 由于您的评分
Okay, well, due to your ranking…
你好 恰克 好名字啊
Hi there. Chuck! Great name.
- 谢谢 - 今晚过得还好吧
- Thank you. - Hope you're having a great night.
- 挺好的 - 我要租一辆车
- It's pretty good. - So I need a car.
- 您有想要的车型吗 - 什么都行
- You got a vehicle in mind? - Anything, really.
嗯 由于您当前的排位
Well, due to your current ranking,
只能给您我们的特廉车队
you're restricted to our super saver fleet.
- 啊 这样啊 好 - I-巡航者2号
- Yep. That's… Yeah. - I-Cruiser 2?
这年头还有2号啊
They still have the 2?
呃 老天
Oh, God.
啊 不是吧
Oh, come on.
呃
Uh…
妈蛋
Damn it!
当时我们在艺术夏令营里 只是才五岁的小女孩
The little girl, who when we were both five years old in art camp,
主动找我说话 因为她看见我害怕了
started talking to me because she saw I was scared.
她帮我做了破布先生
The girl who helped me make Mr. Rags…
此时该落泪 人群为你狂热 你可以做到的
Teardrop. Crowd goes wild. You can do this.
- 抱歉啊 我保证我已经在路上了 - 你到哪儿了
- Sorry, okay, I swear I'm on my way. - How far away are you?
呃 还有点远呢 我错过了航班
Uh… Quite a ways. I missed my flight.
- 你说什么 - 呃 也不算错过 就是
- What? - Well, not missed it but…
所以你赶不上晚宴彩排了吗
So you're not gonna make the rehearsal dinner?
- 赶不上了 - 莱希
- No. - Lacie!
实在很抱歉 今天真的
I am so sorry. It's been…
我租了一辆车 正往那边开呢
I got a rental car. I'm driving.
开车 这得开九个小时吧
Driving? That's like nine hours.
我开得很快的
I'm making good time,
开上一夜 就当是公路旅行了
gonna go through the night, make a road trip out of it.
没什么问题吧
Is everything okay?
要是有的话我可以找人替你的
I can find a replacement if something's wrong.
别 别 别 我会准时到的 我以破布先生的名义发誓
No. No. No. I'll be there. I swear on Mr. Rags.
哈哈哈
Ha ha ha!
那好吧 路上小心
Okay, just drive safe!
一定的 我就
You bet. I'll just…
拜托
Come on.
拜托啊
求你了
Please.
好了
Okay.
你想干嘛啊
What do you want?
我去
Oh, shit.
你好 不好意思
Hi. Sorry.
你们的充电器跟我的车不匹配
Your charger doesn't fit my car.
- 这种车现在可少见了 - 是租的
- Don't see those around much these days. - It's a rental.
我们的充电器是Q2Z型的 你的是K1型 他们没给你适配器吗
Ours chargers are Q2Z, yours one's a K1. They didn't give you an adapter?
没有 你们这儿有吗
No. Do you have one?
- 我这没有 你到处问问吧 - 好吧 谢谢
- Not in here. Ask around. - Thanks, anyway.
你帮大忙了
You're super helpful.
两星
Two stars?!
为什么给我打两星
Two stars?
刚刚不算什么有意义的交流
Wasn't a meaningful encounter.
不好意思 先生
Sir, excuse me.
不好意思
Excuse me, sorry.
请问你有K1型适配器吗
Do you have a K1 adapter, by any chance?
你呢 女士 请问有K1型适配器吗 要不看看后备箱
Ma'am, how about you, a K1 adapter, perhaps, in the trunk of your car?
好吧
Sure.
真好
Great.
噢 女士 你好 请问你有K1型适配器吗
Oh, ma'am, hi. Do you have a K1 adapter?
我租了一辆车 它
I have a rental car. It's…
- 慢点 让她搭个便车吧 - 她的评分才2.8
- Slow down. Let's give her a ride. - She's, like, 2.8.
别这样啊
Come on!
我什么都没干吧
I didn't even do anything!
你好像需要搭车啊
You look like you need a ride.
呃
Um…
其实 不用了 我没事
Actually, I'm okay.
看着可不像没事 上来吧 我不咬人
Don't look it. Come on. I don't bite.
有啤酒 咖啡 红酒 威士忌 别客气
Luther, Mrs. Coffee, reds, whiskey. Help yourself.
不用了 谢谢
I'm okay. Thanks.
你去哪里
Where are you headed?
呃 尽量到玛丽港附近就好了
Uh… Just as close as you can get to Port Mary would be great.
想从我发的东西里看出我是不是危险人物吧
Checking my feed for danger signs?
常有的事 才1.4分 肯定是个反社会的疯子 对吧
I get it a lot. 1.4 gotta be an antisocial maniac, right?
- 你看起来 - 正常吗
- You seem… - Normal?
- 是啊 - 谢了
- Yeah. - Thank you.
花了点心思的 你怎么回事
It took some effort. What happened to you?
我说 你2.8分 但看起来不像2.8啊
I mean, you're a 2.8, but you don't look 2.8.
那个不是 这是暂时的
That's not… This is temporary.
- 我会升上去的 - 嗯哼
- I'm gonna turn it around. - Uh-huh.
- 我要去参加一个婚礼 我是首席伴娘 - 挺好
- I'm going to a wedding. Maid of honour. - Nice.
想听听我的致辞吗
Wanna hear my speech?
不想
No.
所以你是怎么掉到2.8的
So how come you're a 2.8?
唉 我在机场因为吼人被罚分了
Well, I got marked down at the airport for yelling,
还被上了双倍扣分的状态
and they put me on double damage.
- 感觉怎么样 - 糟透了
- How did it feel? - Awful.
我是说吼人
I meant the yelling.
不晓得 我当时很生气
I don't know. I was mad.
真是把我害惨了
Look at where it got me.
但只要我赶上了婚礼 做好我的致辞
But as long as I get to the wedding, do the speech,
他们就不会在意我的2.8了 我毕竟是跟新娘一起的
they'll overlook the 2.8. I'm with the bride.
如果我干得好 那些人可都是接近五分的
And if I do well, well, they're all high fours.
我的评分曲线就能往上走了
so that velocitates my arc.
然后等我的罚分取消了 我的平均分能涨一大截
And once they lift the point penalty, well, my average goes way up,
所以 嗯 会没事的
and, yeah, it's gonna be okay.
天 你跟我还真像
God, you remind me of me.
- 唔 - 不是现在的我
- Hmm. - Not now.
我曾经 到过4.6分
I was, uh… 4.6 once.
- 4.6 - 当时评分就是天啊
- 4.6? - Used to live for it.
我那叫一个拼命啊
All the work I put in…
八年前 我老公汤姆 得了癌症
Eight years ago, Tom, my husband, got cancer.
是胰腺癌 非常糟心 到了晚期才出现症状
It was pancreatic. It was a real bitch. The symptoms showed up late.
我很难过
I'm so sorry.
咱俩并不认识 你不是真心难过
You don't know me so you're not really sorry.
主要是因为我突然开始讲癌症 让你觉得尴尬了
You're just mainly awkward 'cause I have sprung some cancer talk at you.
总之 我给每个医生
Anyway, I five-starred every doctor,
每个护士 每个四星精英的顾问都打了五星
every nurse, every high-four consultant that we had.
叮 叮 叮 非常感谢
Ding. Ding. Ding. Thank you so much.
然而癌症才不管你呢 该扩散还是扩散了
The cancer didn't give a shit. It just kept growing.
几个月后 我们听说了一种实验性的疗法
A couple of months in, we heard about this experimental treatment.
非常昂贵 只对极少数人开放
It was very expensive. It was very exclusive.
我竭尽全力想给他争取一个名额
I did everything I could to get him a spot there.
汤姆当时的评分是4.3
Tom was a 4.3.
他们把他的床位给了一个4.4分的
They gave his bed to a 4.4.
所以当他过世的时候 我想 去他娘的
So when he died I thought, fuck it.
我开始在任何场合都直言不讳
I started saying what I wanted, when I wanted.
有什么就说什么
Just drop it out there.
这种做法并不讨喜
People don't always like that.
你一旦开始这么做 你的评分
It is incredible how fast you slip off the ladder.
就会飞速下滑
when you start doing that.
我发现我有很多朋友都不喜欢诚实
It turned out a lot of my friends didn't care for honesty.
对我的态度就像是我在他们的早餐桌上拉了一坨粑粑似的
Treated me like I had taken a shit at their breakfast table.
但是 天啊 有话直说的感觉棒极了
But, Jesus Christ, it felt good.
摆脱那些混蛋
Shedding those fuckers.
就像脱掉挤脚的鞋一样
It was like taking off tight shoes.
- 或许你该试试 - 哦 算了
- Maybe you should try it? - Oh, come on.
为什么不呢
Why not?
我不能踢掉鞋子 就这么光着脚走吧
I can't just kick off my shoes and walk the earth or whatever.
- 你不试试怎么知道 - 只是
- You won't know unless you try. - Oh, that's just…
听着 你的人生原本丰富多彩
Look, you had something with your life,
真实的 美好的时光 你却全部失去了 我很遗憾
real things, good things, and you lost it all, and I'm sorry.
所以现在你已经没什么可丢弃的了
So now you've got nothing left to lose.
但是我甚至都没有什么值得丢弃的事情
But I don't even have the something worth losing, not yet.
我是说 我仍在为此努力奋斗
You know, I mean, I'm still fighting for that.
- “此”是指什么 - 我不知道 能让我感觉充实的人生吧
- And what is "that"? - I don't know. Enough to be content?
比如 环顾四周 心里想 我过得还不错
Like, to look around and think, well, I guess I'm okay.
能好好地松一口气 而不是感觉 感觉
Just to be able to breathe out, not feeling like… like…
感觉 而这个境界还太遥远了 太太遥远了
Like just… And that is way off, like, way, way off.
到达之前 我还是得玩数字游戏
And until I get there, I have to play the numbers game.
我们都得这样 环境就是如此 这个该死的世界就是这么运转的
We all do, that's what we're in. That's how the fucking world works.
听着 或许你不记得了 你只是年纪太大无法理解了
Look, maybe you don't remember, you know, you're just too old to get it.
我不是那个意思
I do not mean that how it sounds.
别担心 我不会给你差评的
Don't worry. I'm not voting you down.
- 宝贝儿 - 几点了
- Sweetheart. - What time is it?
我从这里要往东走了 你得找别人搭便车了
I'm heading east from here so I think you need to get yourself another ride.
- 我们在哪里 - 距离玛丽港口30英里远
- Where are we? - About 30 miles from Port Mary.
这边有很多公交车 你会一切顺利的
A lot of buses stop here so you should be fine.
- 嗯 谢谢你 - 祝你致辞成功
- Well, thank you. - Good luck with your speech.
我给你在里面放了点小东西
I put a little something in there for you.
- 是嘛 - 紧急逃离舱口
- You did? - Emergency escape hatch!
再见
Bye.
在这个世界上 我们都过于关注
In this world, we're all so caught up…
自己演的独角戏
…in our own dramas.
- 我爸 - 很容易忽视了真正重要的东西
- So, Dad was like… - It's easy to forget what matters.
他从来没有听说过这个剧
He'd never even heard of the show.
我说 “你居然从来没听说过《宁静海》”
I'm like, "You never heard of Sea of Tranquillity?"
这可是最棒的科幻作品
Like, the number-one sci-fi fantasy,
而他只会说“什么鬼” 算了
and he's all like, "What the fuck?" Whatever!
我想我对这种紫色有点过敏
I think I'm allergic to this purple.
所以我就说 “我要去玛丽港口的宁静海剧迷大会
So I'm like, "Well, I'm going to Tranquillity Con in Port Mary.
所以我才打扮成达斯特中尉”
That's why I'm dressed like Lieutenant Duster."
他一脸 “呃 玛丽港口好几英里远啊”
He's all like, "Uh… Port Mary is frickin' miles away."
啥啥啥的
Yadda, yadda, yadda.
他给我打了一颗星 呃 谢了 老爸
He one-stars me. Like, thanks, Dad.
- 回去再见 - 好的
- See you back on there. - Okay.
你们是要去《宁静海》剧迷大会吗
Are you guys headed to Tranquillity Con?
- 你喜欢《宁静号》么 - 骨灰级粉丝啊
- You're into Sea of Tranquillity? - Totally.
我都准备好过去了
I was all set to go.
我一个朋友 拿着我的服装 已经过去了 但是我的车抛锚了
My friend, who is there already, has my costume, but my car broke down.
我们的房车里还有位置
Well, there's some space in the RV.
- 嗨 - 嘿
- Hi. - Hey!
- 你是宁粉 对吧 - 抱歉你说什么
- You're a Trank head, huh? - Sorry?
宁粉 《宁静海》的粉丝啊
Trank head. Sea of Tranquillity fan?
对的 我们那边一般都说宁饭
Oh, yeah. We say Tranksters where I'm from.
- 你最喜欢的角色是谁 - 必须是达斯特中尉啊
- Who's your favourite character? - Gotta be Lieutenant Duster.
- 她太牛逼了 - 她
- She's awesome. - She?
他 我说错了
He! I misspoke.
达斯特中尉没有固定的性别
Lieutenant Duster has no fixed gender.
我知道 所以才很难记住 对吧
I know, and that's why it's so hard to remember, right?
不好意思 接个电话
Excuse me. Gotta get this.
我的朋友 正在大会上
My friend, at the convention.
嗨 奈
Hi, Nay!
天呐 昨晚太疯狂了 不过我已经快到了
So, oh, my God, insane night, but I am so close now.
别来了
Don't come.
什么 不不不 我再一个小时就到了啊
What? No. No. I'm, like, an hour away.
别来了 我不想让你来
Don't come. I don't want you here.
我不知道你怎么了 但是我不能让一个2.6分的人出现在我的婚礼上
I don't know what is up with you, but I cannot have a 2.6 at my wedding.
不 那是暂时的 暂时的
Oh, no, that's temporary! That's temporary.
婚礼就在今天 所以
Well, the wedding's today so…
- 但是这也没改变什么啊 - 莱希
- But it doesn't change anything. - Lacie…
- 我还是能致辞的 - 莱希
- I can still do the same speech. - Lacie…
- 还有破布先生 - 不行
- And there's Mr. Rags! - No!
但是 但是你邀请了我
But… But you invited me.
你看过宾客名单了 他们都是 4.5分或者以上
You've seen the guest list. They are all, like, 4.5 or above.
他们看到你这个2.6分会爆炸的 我承受不了那种伤害
They are going to freak at a 2.6, and I am not taking that kind of damage,
再加上我有大概六个月 没下降到4.7了
plus I haven't dipped under a 4.7 in, like, six months.
你说你想见见交情最久的老朋友了
You said you wanted your oldest friend.
当我请你发言的时候 你是4.2分 好吗
When I asked you to speak, you were a 4.2, okay?
请一个四星出头的老朋友出现在这样的场合 这种真实性
And the authenticity of a vintage bond low four at a gathering of this calibre.
在我们做的所有模拟中 效果都非常完美
played fantastically on all the stimulations we ran.
预测至少都能给我们加上0.2分
Forecast was a prestige bounce of 0.2 minimum.
但现在你连三分都不到了 对不起
But now you're a sub three. Sorry.
那只会激起过多得流言蜚语
That just puts the stink on things a little too much.
对我们来说是负面影响
That just plays badly for us.
所以这一切对你来说只是数字么
So it was just about numbers for you?
噢 别装了 对咱俩来说都只是数字好么
Oh, cut the shit! It was numbers for both of us.
你也想让精英们给你好评的 别否认
You wanted those primo votes, don't deny it.
你自己又没法获得精英的评分 别自欺欺人了
It's not like you could get them on your own. Let's not kid ourselves.
我 我会让他们给我好评的
Oh, I'm… I'm getting those votes.
怎样 你就打算随随便便地出现 让大家都喜欢你么
What? You're just gonna roll up here and make people like you?
- 对 我要去致辞 - 不 你不能
- That's right. I'm doing my speech. - No, you're not.
我要去 而且他们听过之后 会给我疯狂点赞的
Yes, I am. And they are gonna vote me through the roof when they hear it.
- 他们会感动得泪流满面的 - 你给我回家
- Weep their fucking eyes out! - Go home!
喂
Hello?
靠
Fuck!
我从来没看过你们那个傻逼剧
I have never seen your stupid fucking show.
希望它被砍
Hope they cancel it!
我要搭个便车
I need a ride!
妈蛋
Fuck!
天啊
Jesus!
嘿 嘿
Hey! Hey!
嘿
Hey!
- 能借用一下你的摩托车吗 - 什么
- Can I borrow your bike? - What?
能借用一下你的摩托车吗
Can I borrow your bike?
奈奥米•杰恩•布雷斯托 你是否愿意 让这个男人成为你的丈夫
Do you, Naomi Jayne Blestow, take this man to be your husband,
遵守婚姻契约 与他一起生活
to live together with him in the covenant of marriage?
爱他 慰藉他
To love him, comfort him,
尊敬他 守护他 不论健康疾病
honour and keep him, in sickness and in health…
抛弃一切 忠诚于他
and forsaking all others, be faithful unto him…
敬我最好的兄弟 安东尼 他是最棒的
To my best mate, Anthony. Let's hear it for him.
打一开始你就在我身边 我爱你 兄弟 感谢你陪我一路走来
You've been there from day one. I love you, man. I appreciate you.
对了 你的致辞太有趣了 以你的标准来说
Hilarious speech, by the way. By your standards.
- 乓乓乓 - 哦哦哦
- Pow! Pow! Pow! - Oh! Oh! Oh!
他还留着几发子弹 哦 兄弟
He's still got a few bullets left. Oh, man.
天啊 呃
Oh, gosh, well, um…
该死
Shit!
我们有很多想感谢的人 我们美丽的伴娘团
We have so many people to thank. Our beautiful bridesmaids.
但是 当然
But, of course,
我最真诚 最温暖的感谢
my most heartfelt thanks, my warmest thanks,
要送给我最好的朋友
are to someone who's my best friend,
我的爱人 如今我可以自豪地宣布 我的妻子
my lover and now, I'm honoured to say, my wife.
奈奥米
Naomi!
一 二 三 奈奥米
One, two, three! Naomi!
冠军之队
The A Team!
我太爱你了 亲爱的
I love you so much, darl.
哇哦 哇哦 哇哦 哇哦
Whoo-whoo-whoo-whoo!
恭喜你 先生
Congratulations, sir.
- 谢谢 - 不 应该谢谢你
- Thank you. - No, thank you.
到这边来
Get over here!
快滚过来
Get your ass over here.
过来 小兔崽子
Get in here, big boy.
你帅爆了
You're beautiful!
耶 来击个掌 选的不错
Yeah! Gimme five! Good choice!
这他妈是你应得的 真他妈是你应得的
You fucking earned it, man. You fucking earned it.
大家好
Everybody, hello!
- 噢 我的天啊 - 我爱你
- Oh, my God. - I love you.
大家能安静一下吗
Can everyone be quiet for a moment?
谢谢大家
Thank you.
- 把她弄走 - 那样影响太不好了
- Get rid of her. - That would play awful.
她他妈只能得1.1分
She's a fucking 1.1.
我想对那些不认识我的人说 那个 你们都不认识我
Now for those of you who don't know me, which is… all of you…
我叫莱希•庞德
my name is Lacie Pound.
不管你们信不信 我是奈奥米交情最久的朋友之一
and, believe it or not, I am one of Naomi's oldest friends.
嗨 奈奈
Hi, Nay-Nay!
我也很高兴见到你 保罗 我听说过很多你的事
It's great to meet you too, Paul. I've heard a lot about you.
他可是个大人物 那个保罗
He's a pretty big deal, that Paul.
大人物
Pretty big deal.
他能自己做橄榄酱 太棒了
He makes his own tapenade! Yeah.
呃
Uh…
不管怎么说 呃 我
Anyway, um… I…
这一辈子都很向往奈奥米
have looked up to Naomi pretty much my entire life.
从我们五岁第一次见面
We met when we were five years old,
一直到十几岁的时候 我们俩简直是一对无敌组合
and right up through to our teenage years, we made quite the pair.
我们聊各种女生话题
We'd talk about all the things girls talk about,
你懂的 男孩 发型 小玩意儿 呃 还是男孩
you know, boys, hair, products, uh… more boys.
有时我会尝试稍微聊聊别的话题
I mean, I tried sometimes to expand our range a little.
比如气候变化 但是她觉得有些无聊
and talk about climate change, but she found that kind of boring so…
继续
Go on.
她可能是对的 我是说 地球算啥啊 对吗
She was probably right. I mean, fuck the planet, right?
哇
Whoo!
好的 谢谢你 来吧 我们嗨起来吧
Yes, thank you! Come on. Let's have a little fun here.
你们懂的 地球算个毛啊
You know, fuck the planet!
管它作死啊
Fuck the planet!
不管怎么说
Anyway…
我这辈子几乎一直都在向往奈奥米
I… looked up to Naomi pretty much my entire life,
也就是说她一直在居高临下地鄙视我
which meant she was looking down on me.
脸上倒是永远带笑的
Always with a smile though.
上高中的时候 她是我可以靠着哭的臂膀
In high school, she was my shoulder to cry on.
她好像很喜欢那样 我跟男生总是没法顺利交往
She seemed to enjoy that. Guys and me never worked out.
他们看到奈奥米就就会这样 然后你们懂的 就没有然后了
They'd see Naomi and just… Whoo! You know, that was it.
她有紧绷绷的小翘臀
She had this tight ass,
就像两个小拳头
like two fists.
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
而我就像
I was all like…
就像这样
I was like…
穿过学校的走廊
through the hallways in high school.
但她却在我身边
And she was there for me.
当我跪在马桶前呕吐的时候
Holding my hair back…
帮我挽起头发
as I knelt, vomiting, in front of the crapper.
对此我很感谢 奈奥米
Thank you for that, Naomi.
我一直希望我是你
I always wished I was you.
而且
And…
我猜那就是你一直和我待在一起的原因吧
I guess that's why you kept me around so long?
直到有一天你有了新工作
Until you got your new job.
和你高大上的新朋友
and your fancy new friends.
还有那个
And that…
操他妈的混蛋
…fucking… jackhole!
然后你就不需要我了 你可能已经找到了我的替代品
And you didn't need me. You probably got another me.
我猜你又像女妖一样勾搭上了新的小婊子闺蜜了吧
Guess there's some other "yeth Beth" you moved on to like a succubus.
我就要说到破布先生了 好吗 日
I'm getting to Mr. Rags, okay? Jesus!
退后
Stay back.
给我特么后退 我会杀了他
Stay the fuck back! I'll kill him!
我会把他的头切下来 塞进屁眼里
I'll cut his head off and stick it up my ass!
时间马上就要到了
Time's nearly up!
- 嗨 冷静一点 - 我
- Hey! Calm down. - I…
我只想说 在这个深陷于我们自身麻烦的世界里
I just wanted to say, in this world so caught up in our own shit,
- 我们不要忘记了最重要的东西 - 没事的 没事的
- let's not forget what matters. - It's okay. It's okay.
幸福 去你妈的保罗和奈奥米 她就是
Happiness, fucking Paul and Naomi, and she's…
她 她干了格雷格
She… She fucked Greg!
我知道她这么做了
I know she did.
- 我知道你这么做了 - 不
- I know you did. - No…
你别想否认
Don't even try to deny…
当时我们在艺术夏令营里 只是才五岁的小女孩
The little girl who, when we were just five-years-old in art camp,
她主动和我说话 只因为看出了我很害怕
started talking to me because she saw I was scared.
她还帮我做了破布先生
and helped me make Mr. Rags.
它让我时时想起你 想起你对我是多么重要
He reminds me of you and what you meant to me then!
我真的很荣幸能在这里见证你的狗屁婚礼
And I'm so honoured to be here to see this shit!
我爱你 奈奈 我一直爱着你
I love you, Nay-Nay! I've always loved you!
我爱你
I love you!
你他妈在看什么
What the fuck are you looking at?
我一直在想的东西
Just what I was wondering.
那
Well…
别
Don't!
别什么 别疑惑吗
Don't? Don't wonder?
嗯哼
Uh-huh.
没有疑惑这将是个无聊的世界
It would be a dull world without wonder.
我对你的世界一点也不感兴趣
I don't give a shit about your world.
我不喜欢你的胸罩
I don't like your brassiere.
我不喜欢你的胡子
I don't like your moustache.
我不喜欢你的气场
I don't like your aura.
- 我的气场 - 是的
- My aura? - Yeah.
我不喜欢你的 头
I don't like your… head.
你这个头是什么鬼
Your entire head is just ridiculous to me.
真的吗
Really?
你看起来就像一个醉酒成性 过气的气象播报员
You look like an alcoholic former weatherman.
你听起来就像一只就像刚听说
You sound like a lost little lamb.
世界上没有圣诞老人的迷路的小羔羊
that just got told there's no Santa Claus.
你妈是被哪个卡通人物上了
What sort of cartoon character did your mum have to fuck.
才生出的你这个怪胎
to brew you up in the womb?
至少我像是生出来的
At least I look like I was born,
而不是在地下实验室被一头受虐待的奶牛拉出来的屎
not shit out by some tormented cow creature in an underground lab.
你还被那个实验室丢出去了呢
You got tossed out of that lab.
- 哦 是吗 - 噢 是啊 直接从马桶里冲下去
- Oh, yeah? - Oh, yeah, flushed out.
- 噢 - 掉在垃圾堆里
- Ooh! - In the trash!
- 你的脸他妈像是 - 去你的
- Your face is a fucking… - Fucking.
他妈的生化爆炸的车祸现场
Fucking biological car crash.
能让毕加索翻白眼 然后说
that made Picasso screw his eyes up and say,
““呵呵 根本看不懂”
"Well, that just don't make sense."
- 你他妈就是个混蛋 - 去你的
- You're a fucking asshole. - Fuck you!
- 下周三干死你 - 圣诞节榨干你
- Fuck you next Wednesday. - Fuck you for Christmas!
- 操死你 - 日翻你
- Fuck you! - Fuck you!